University of Connecticut 1998.0185
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series I: Correspondence, 1935-1962
  - 1939-1940
    - Ledgebrook committee on agriculture (Box 3:, Folder 75)
    - Longley, R. I. (Box 3:, Folder 76)
    - Manchester, Harry G. (Box 3:, Folder 77)
    - McDonough, Edward J. (Box 3:, Folder 78)
    - M (Box 3:, Folder 79)
    - Military correspondence (Box 3:, Folder 80)
    - N (Box 3:, Folder 81)
    - P (Box 3:, Folder 82)
    - Personnel Department (Box 3:, Folder 83)
    - Public Works Commissioner (Box 3:, Folder 84)
    - Ra - Rn (Box 3:, Folder 85)
    - Registrar's office (Box 3:, Folder 86)
    - Reorganization material (Box 3:, Folder 87)
    - Reorganization of education, 1939-1940 (Box 3:, Folder 88)
    - Riccio, Leonard C. (Box 3:, Folder 89)
    - S (Box 3:, Folder 90)
    - Sabbatical leave (Box 3:, Folder 91)
    - Scholarship Loan Committee (Box 3:, Folder 92)
    - Slate, W. L. (Box 3:, Folder 93)
    - Spencer, Samuel R. (Box 3:, Folder 94)
    - State universities (Box 3:, Folder 95)
    - Student Senate minutes (Box 3:, Folder 96)
    - T (Box 4:, Folder 1)
    - Travel letters, 1939-1940 (Box 4:, Folder 2)
    - Trumbull Fellowship (Box 4:, Folder 3)
    - Trustees (Box 4:, Folder 4)
    - U.S.D.A. (Box 4:, Folder 5)
    - U.S. Office of Education (Box 4:, Folder 6)
    - University extension July - August (Box 4:, Folder 7)
    - University extension September (Box 4:, Folder 8)
    - University extension October - December (Box 4:, Folder 9)
    - Van Bibber, George (Box 4:, Folder 10)
    - W (Box 4:, Folder 11)
    - Waugh, Albert E. (Box 4:, Folder 12)
    - White, G. C. (Box 4:, Folder 13)
  - 1940-1941
    - A (Box 4:, Folder 14)
    - Ackerman, Laurence J. (Box 4:, Folder 15)
    - Agricultural industries building (Box 4:, Folder 16)
    - American Association of University Women (Box 4:, Folder 17)
    - Armory and airport hangar (Box 4:, Folder 18)
    - Association of Land Grant Colleges (Box 4:, Folder 19)
    - Association of Land Grant Colleges (Box 4:, Folder 20)
    - B (Box 4:, Folder 21)
    - Baldwin, Raymond E. (Box 4:, Folder 22)
    - Biographical data (Box 4:, Folder 23)
    - Brammel, P. Roy (Box 4:, Folder 24)
    - Buckley, John (Box 4:, Folder 25)
    - C (Box 4:, Folder 26)
    - Commencement (Box 4:, Folder 27)
    - Connecticut College of Pharmacy (Box 4:, Folder 28)
    - Clapp, Raymond K. (Box 4:, Folder 29)
    - Danaher, John re: armory (Box 4:, Folder 30)
    - Department of Public Works (Box 4:, Folder 31)
    - Division of military science and tactics (Box 4:, Folder 32)
    - Dole, Sumner A. (Box 4:, Folder 33)
    - Donning, W. H. (Box 4:, Folder 34)
    - E (Box 4:, Folder 35)
    - Equipment requests (Box 4:, Folder 36)
    - Executive Committee (Box 4:, Folder 37)
    - F (Box 4:, Folder 38)
    - Federal Security Agency, U. S. Office of Education (Box 4:, Folder 39)
    - French, Mildred P. (Box 4:, Folder 40)
    - G (Box 4:, Folder 41)
    - Gentry, C.B., 1940-1941 (Box 4:, Folder 42)
    - Grace, Alonzo G. (Box 4:, Folder 43)
    - Greene, Harry A. (Box 4:, Folder 44)
    - H (Box 4:, Folder 45)
    - Haggerty, William J. (Box 4:, Folder 46)
    - Honorary Recognition (Box 4:, Folder 47)
    - Hurley, Robert A. - Governor (Box 4:, Folder 48)
    - Iowa State Board of Education (Box 4:, Folder 49)
    - J (Box 4:, Folder 50)
    - Jorgensen, A. N. - speeches (Box 4:, Folder 51)
    - K (Box 4:, Folder 52)
    - L (Box 4:, Folder 53)
    - Lampe, J. H. - correspondence (Box 4:, Folder 54)
    - Lampe, J. H. - Engineer's Council for Professional Development (Box 4:, Folder 55)
    - Lampe, J. H. - School of Engineering (Box 4:, Folder 56)
    - Longley, R. I. (Box 4:, Folder 57)
    - M (Box 4:, Folder 58)
    - Maloney, Francis T. re: armory (Box 4:, Folder 59)
    - McDonough, Edward J. Jr. (Box 4:, Folder 60)
    - Miller, William J. re: armory (Box 4:, Folder 61)
    - N (Box 4:, Folder 62)
    - National Association of State Universities (Box 4:, Folder 63)
    - P (Box 4:, Folder 64)
    - Pallotti, Francis A. (Box 4:, Folder 65)
    - Pratt and Whitney Aircraft (Box 4:, Folder 66)
    - R (Box 4:, Folder 67)
    - Registrar (Box 4:, Folder 68)
    - Retirement commission (Box 4:, Folder 69)
    - Riccio, L. C. (Box 4:, Folder 70)
    - S (Box 4:, Folder 71)
    - Sabbatical requests (Box 4:, Folder 72)
    - Stanley, James (Box 4:, Folder 73)
    - State Budget Committee (Box 4:, Folder 74)
    - Straker, Robert A. (Box 4:, Folder 75)
    - T (Box 4:, Folder 76)
    - Theta Kappa Phi - fraternity (Box 4:, Folder 77)
    - V (Box 4:, Folder 78)
    - W (Box 4:, Folder 79)
    - Wadhams, J. H. re: armory (Box 4:, Folder 80)
    - Waugh, Albert E. (Box 4:, Folder 81)
    - Whetten, Nathan L. (Box 4:, Folder 82)
    - White, George C. (Box 4:, Folder 83)
    - Whitney name controversy (Box 4:, Folder 84)
    - Wilson, M. L., 1940-1941 (Box 4:, Folder 85)
    - Wish, Fred D., Jr. (Box 4:, Folder 86)
    - Wood, Walter C. (Box 4:, Folder 87)
    - Woodward, E. G. (Box 4:, Folder 88)
  - 1941-1942
    - A (Box 4:, Folder 89)
    - Alumni - geographic lists (Box 4:, Folder 90)
    - Appointments, tenure and promotions (Box 4:, Folder 91)
    - Armory (Box 4:, Folder 92)
    - Attorney General (Box 4:, Folder 93)
    - Audio - visual center (Box 4:, Folder 94)
    - Auerbach, Beatrice Fox (Box 4:, Folder 95)
    - B (Box 4:, Folder 96)
    - Board of Higher Education (Box 4:, Folder 97)
    - Brammell, P. Roy (Box 4:, Folder 98)
    - Budget department (Box 4:, Folder 99)
    - Busses (Box 4:, Folder 100)
    - C (Box 4:, Folder 101)
    - Civilian Defense (Box 4:, Folder 102)
    - College of Pharmacy (Box 4:, Folder 103)
    - Commencement (Box 4:, Folder 104)
    - Committee reports (Box 4:, Folder 105)
    - Connecticut State Grange (Box 4:, Folder 106)
    - D (Box 5:, Folder 1)
    - Defense Council (state) (Box 5:, Folder 2)
    - Development commission (Box 5:, Folder 3)
    - E (Box 5:, Folder 4)
    - F (Box 5:, Folder 5)
    - Faculty stories for newspapers (Box 5:, Folder 6)
    - Finance commissioner (Box 5:, Folder 7)
    - Fox, Lewis (Box 5:, Folder 8)
    - Future of the University of Connecticut (Box 5:, Folder 9)
    - G (Box 5:, Folder 10)
    - Gentry, C.B. (Box 5:, Folder 11)
    - Grace, Alonzo G. (Box 5:, Folder 12)
    - Haggerty, William J. (Box 5:, Folder 13)
    - Hicks laboratory and classroom building - equipment (Box 5:, Folder 14)
    - He - Ho (Box 5:, Folder 15)
    - Honorary Recognition (Box 5:, Folder 16)
    - Hook, James W. (Box 5:, Folder 17)
    - Hurley, Robert A. - Governor (Box 5:, Folder 18)
    - J, 1941-1942 (Box 5:, Folder 19)
    - Jorgensen, A. N. (Box 5:, Folder 20)
    - K (Box 5:, Folder 21)
    - Lampe, J. H. (Box 5:, Folder 22)
    - Li - Lz (Box 5:, Folder 23)
    - Longley, R. I. (Box 5:, Folder 24)
    - M (Box 5:, Folder 25)
    - Menzinger, Fred J. (Box 5:, Folder 26)
    - Military correspondence (Box 5:, Folder 27)
    - Marsh, H. W. (Box 5:, Folder 28)
    - N (Box 5:, Folder 29)
    - Nursing, School of (Box 5:, Folder 30)
    - Pratt and Whitney Aircraft (Box 5:, Folder 31)
    - Price, S. Willard (Box 5:, Folder 32)
    - Public Works Department (Box 5:, Folder 33)
    - Religious education (Box 5:, Folder 34)
    - Riccio, L. C. (Box 5:, Folder 35)
    - Reorganization of education (Box 5:, Folder 36)
    - S (Box 5:, Folder 37)
    - Sabbatical leave (Box 5:, Folder 38)
    - Scholarship loan funds (Box 5:, Folder 39)
    - Selective service -, January - June (Box 5:, Folder 40)
    - Selective service -, July - December (Box 5:, Folder 41)
    - Social Work, School of (Box 5:, Folder 42)
    - State universities (Box 5:, Folder 43)
    - Student meeting, 1942 January 9 (Box 5:, Folder 44)
    - Student Senate (Box 5:, Folder 45)
    - T (Box 5:, Folder 46)
    - Trustee appointments, 1942 (Box 5:, Folder 47)
    - Van Bibber, George (Box 5:, Folder 48)
    - W (Box 5:, Folder 49)
    - Waugh, Albert E. (Box 5:, Folder 50)
    - Woodward, E. G. (Box 5:, Folder 51)
    - Y - Z (Box 5:, Folder 52)
  - 1942-1943
    - Anonymous correspondence (Box 5:, Folder 53)
    - Defense and war activities (Box 5:, Folder 54)
    - Selective service (Box 5:, Folder 55)
  - 1944-1945
    - Gentry, C.B., 1944 - 1945 (Box 5:, Folder 56)
  - 1945-1946
    - Baldwin, Raymond E. (Box 5:, Folder 56a)
    - Newton, H. D., 1945
    - Stemmons, Walter
  - 1947-1948
    - Ackerman, Laurence J. (Box 5:, Folder 57)
    - Administrative report (Box 5:, Folder 58)
    - Attorney General (Box 5:, Folder 59)
    - Bond commission (Box 5:, Folder 60)
    - Budget department (state) (Box 5:, Folder 61)
    - Building program (Box 5:, Folder 62)
    - Business projects (Box 5:, Folder 63)
    - Commencement (Box 5:, Folder 64)
    - Comptroller's office (state), July - December (Box 5:, Folder 65)
    - Comptroller's office (state), January - June (Box 5:, Folder 66)
    - Congress (Box 5:, Folder 67)
    - Connecticut's veterans, reemployment advisory commission. (Box 5:, Folder 68)
    - Contracts and agreements (Box 5:, Folder 69)
    - Cronin, John J. (Box 5:, Folder 70)
    - D (Box 5:, Folder 71)
    - Education, State Department (Box 5:, Folder 72)
    - Experiment station (Box 5:, Folder 73)
    - Export packaging (Box 5:, Folder 74)
    - F (Box 5:, Folder 75)
    - Federal public housing agency (Box 5:, Folder 76)
    - Federal works agency (Box 5:, Folder 77)
    - Finance commissioner (Box 5:, Folder 78)
    - Fraternities and sororities (Box 5:, Folder 79)
    - L (Box 5:, Folder 80)
    - M (Box 5:, Folder 81)
    - McConaughy, James L. - Governor (Box 5:, Folder 82)
    - Memorial alumni - student union fund (Box 5:, Folder 83)
    - Military department (Box 5:, Folder 84)
    - N (Box 5:, Folder 85)
    - New England Land Grant Colleges (Box 5:, Folder 86)
    - Nutrition Committee (Box 5:, Folder 87)
    - Pi - Pz (Box 5:, Folder 88)
    - R (Box 5:, Folder 89)
    - Riccio, Leonard C. - comptroller (Box 5:, Folder 90)
    - S (Box 5:, Folder 91)
    - Scholarships and gifts, 1947-1948 (Box 5:, Folder 92)
    - Shannon, James C. - Governor (Box 5:, Folder 93)
    - U. S. D. A. (Box 5:, Folder 94)
    - U. S. Maritime Commission (Box 5:, Folder 95)
    - U. S. Office of Education (Box 5:, Folder 96)
    - University Senate (Box 5:, Folder 97)
    - V (Box 5:, Folder 98)
    - Van Bibber, George (Box 5:, Folder 99)
    - Veterans administration (Box 5:, Folder 100)
    - W (Box 5:, Folder 101)
    - Waugh, Albert E. (Box 5:, Folder 102)
    - Whetten, Nathan L. (Box 5:, Folder 103)
    - Young, Wilfred B. (Box 5:, Folder 104)
  - 1948-1949
    - A (Box 5:, Folder 105)
    - Ba - Bh (Box 5:, Folder 106)
    - Bowles, Chester (Box 5:, Folder 107)
    - Brock, C. Raymond (Box 5:, Folder 108)
    - C (Box 5:, Folder 109)
    - Comptroller's Office (state) (Box 5:, Folder 110)
    - Congress (Box 5:, Folder 111)
    - Cronin, John J. (Box 5:, Folder 112)
    - Education - statements (Box 5:, Folder 113)
    - Engleman, F. E. (Box 5:, Folder 114)
    - F (Box 6:, Folder 1)
    - Fort Trumbull (Box 6:, Folder 2)
    - Fraternities and sororities (Box 6:, Folder 3)
    - Gentry, Charles B. (Box 6:, Folder 4)
    - H (Box 6:, Folder 5)
    - Hopkins, Bert E. (Box 6:, Folder 6)
    - Jorgensen, A. N. (Box 6:, Folder 7)
    - Knoblauch, A. L. (Box 6:, Folder 8)
    - Military department (Box 6:, Folder 9)
    - N (Box 6:, Folder 10)
    - Northby, Arwood S. (Box 6:, Folder 11)
    - Pi - Pz (Box 6:, Folder 12)
    - Retirement commission (Box 6:, Folder 13)
    - Riccio, Leonard C. (Box 6:, Folder 14)
    - S (Box 6:, Folder 15)
    - Shanon, James C. (Box 6:, Folder 16)
    - Student Senate (Box 6:, Folder 17)
    - T, 1948-1949 (Box 6:, Folder 18)
    - Teich, Frederic E. (Box 6:, Folder 19)
    - University commercials (Box 6:, Folder 20)
    - U. S. D. A. (Box 6:, Folder 21)
    - U. S. Office of Education (Box 6:, Folder 22)
    - V (Box 6:, Folder 23)
    - Veterinary School (Box 6:, Folder 24)
    - Wa - Wg (Box 6:, Folder 25)
    - Whetten, Nathan L. (Box 6:, Folder 26)
    - Widmer, Carolyn L. (Box 6:, Folder 27)
    - Young, Wilfred B. (Box 6:, Folder 28)
  - 1949-1950
    - A (Box 6:, Folder 29)
    - B (Box 6:, Folder 30)
    - Bond commission (Box 6:, Folder 31)
    - Bowles, Chester (Box 6:, Folder 32)
    - Brammell, P. Roy (Box 6:, Folder 33)
    - Brock, C. Raymond (Box 6:, Folder 34)
    - Castleman, Francis L. (Box 6:, Folder 35)
    - Cerreny, Clara Carolyn (Box 6:, Folder 36)
    - Ch (Box 6:, Folder 37)
    - Co - Ct (Box 6:, Folder 38)
    - Commencement (Box 6:, Folder 39)
    - Comptroller's Office (State) (Box 6:, Folder 40)
    - Congress (Box 6:, Folder 41)
    - Connecticut Council on Higher Education (Box 6:, Folder 42)
    - Cronin, John J. (Box 6:, Folder 43)
    - Ea - En (Box 6:, Folder 44)
    - Education, Reorganization of - comments on report (Box 6:, Folder 45)
    - Education, State Board of - Liaison committee (Box 6:, Folder 46)
    - Education - statements (Box 6:, Folder 47)
    - F (Box 6:, Folder 48)
    - Finance Commission (Box 6:, Folder 49)
    - Football situation at UConn (Box 6:, Folder 50)
    - Fraternities and Sororities (Box 6:, Folder 51)
    - G (Box 6:, Folder 52)
    - Gentry, Charles B. (Box 6:, Folder 53)
    - Hewitt, Harold G. (Box 6:, Folder 54)
    - Hi - Hn (Box 6:, Folder 55)
    - Hook, James W. (Box 6:, Folder 56)
    - Jorgensen, A. N. (Box 6:, Folder 57)
    - Junior College of Physical Therapy, 1949-1950 (Box 6:, Folder 58)
    - Knoblauch, A. L. (Box 6:, Folder 59)
    - Labor unions (Box 6:, Folder 60)
    - Land Grant Colleges (Box 6:, Folder 61)
    - Military department (Box 6:, Folder 62)
    - National Commission on Accrediting (Box 6:, Folder 63)
    - Reorganization of education, December, March (Box 6:, Folder 64)
    - Reorganization of education, April (Box 6:, Folder 65)
    - Riccio, Leonard C. - University Comptroller (Box 6:, Folder 66)
    - Ryan, J. Ray (trustee) (Box 6:, Folder 67)
    - S (Box 6:, Folder 68)
    - Scholarships and gifts (Box 6:, Folder 69)
    - State Department (United States) (Box 6:, Folder 70)
    - Teich, Frederic C. - University Architect (Box 6:, Folder 71)
    - Trail, John M. - Asst. University Comptroller (Box 6:, Folder 72)
    - United States Office on Education (Box 6:, Folder 73)
    - University commercials, D. R. Gherin-Ghelli (Box 6:, Folder 74)
    - Van Bibber, G. E. (Box 6:, Folder 75)
    - Veterans Administration (Box 6:, Folder 76)
    - Vouchers (Box 6:, Folder 77)
    - W (Box 6:, Folder 78)
    - Young, Wilfred B. (Box 6:, Folder 79)
    - Z (Box 6:, Folder 80)
  - 1950-1951
    - A (Box 6:, Folder 81)
    - Ackerman, Laurence J. (Box 6:, Folder 82)
    - Air Force Program (Box 6:, Folder 83)
    - American Council on Education (Box 6:, Folder 84)
    - Associated Student Government - Constitution (Box 6:, Folder 85)
    - B (Box 6:, Folder 86)
    - Bowles, Chester - Governor (Box 6:, Folder 87)
    - Brock, C. Raymond (Trustee) (Box 6:, Folder 88)
    - Budget (Box 6:, Folder 89)
    - C (Box 6:, Folder 90)
    - Christian, Joseph O. (Box 6:, Folder 91)
    - Congress (Box 6:, Folder 92)
    - F (Box 6:, Folder 93)
    - Film production (Box 6:, Folder 94)
    - Fraternities and sororities (Box 6:, Folder 95)
    - Fullbright scholarships (Box 6:, Folder 96)
    - G (Box 6:, Folder 97)
    - H, 1950-1951 (Box 6:, Folder 98)
    - Hewitt, Harold G. (Box 6:, Folder 99)
    - Hook, James W. (trustee) (Box 6:, Folder 100)
    - I - J (Box 6:, Folder 101)
    - Johnson, R. B. (Box 6:, Folder 102)
    - Jorgensen, A. N. (Box 6:, Folder 103)
    - Knoblauch, A. L. (Box 6:, Folder 104)
    - L (Box 6:, Folder 105)
    - Liaison committee on education (Box 6:, Folder 106)
    - Lodge, John Davis (Box 6:, Folder 107)
    - McReynolds, George E. (Box 6:, Folder 108)
    - National Commission on Accrediting (Box 6:, Folder 109)
    - P (Box 6:, Folder 110)
    - R (Box 6:, Folder 111)
    - Riccio, Leonard C. - University Comptroller (Box 6:, Folder 112)
    - S (Box 6:, Folder 113)
    - T (Box 6:, Folder 114)
    - Teich, Frederic C. - University Architect (Box 6:, Folder 115)
    - T. V. (Box 6:, Folder 116)
    - U - V (Box 6:, Folder 117)
    - University commercials (Box 6:, Folder 118)
    - Van Bibber, E. George (Box 6:, Folder 119)
    - Veterinary medicine (Box 6:, Folder 120)
    - Waugh, Albert E. (Box 6:, Folder 121)
    - Young, W. B. (Box 6:, Folder 122)
  - 1951-1952
    - A (Box 6:, Folder 123)
    - Army, Department of (Box 6:, Folder 124)
    - Bequests (Box 6:, Folder 125)
  - 1953-1954
    - Tappan, Frances M. (Box 6:, Folder 126)
    - Technical assistance program (Box 6:, Folder 127)
    - Teich, Frederic C. - University architect (Box 6:, Folder 128)
    - T. V. (Box 7:, Folder 1)
    - Trecker, Harleigh B. (Box 7:, Folder 2)
    - Union board and building (Box 7:, Folder 3)
    - U. S. Department of Agriculture (Box 7:, Folder 4)
    - U. S. Office of Education (Box 7:, Folder 5)
    - University commercials (Box 7:, Folder 6)
    - University Senate, 1953-1954 (Box 7:, Folder 7)
    - Van Bibber, E. G. (Box 7:, Folder 8)
    - W (Box 7:, Folder 9)
    - Waugh, Albert E., July - September (Box 7:, Folder 10)
    - Waugh, Albert E., February - April (Box 7:, Folder 12)
    - Waugh, Albert E., October - January (Box 7:, Folder 11)
    - Waugh, Albert E., May - June (Box 7:, Folder 13)
    - Watson, Elmer S. (Trustee) (Box 7:, Folder 14)
    - Westcott and Mapes, November - March (Box 7:, Folder 15)
    - Westcott and Mapes, April - June (Box 7:, Folder 16)
    - Whetten, Nathan L. (Box 7:, Folder 17)
    - Widmer, Carolyn L. (Box 7:, Folder 18)
    - Young, Wilfred b., July - October (Box 7:, Folder 19)
    - Young, Wilfred B., November - June (Box 7:, Folder 20)
  - 1954-1955
    - A (Box 8:, Folder 1)
    - Ackerman, L. J. - Dean, School of Business (Box 8:, Folder 2)
    - Activities fee (Box 8:, Folder 3)
    - Advisers (Box 8:, Folder 4)
    - Air Force (Box 8:, Folder 5)
    - Air Force Advisory Group, 1955 January 10 (Box 8:, Folder 6)
    - American Council on Education - Arthur S. Adams (Box 8:, Folder 7)
    - American Council on Education - National Scholarship Program (Box 8:, Folder 8)
    - American Institute of Biological Studies (Box 8:, Folder 9)
    - Annual reports (Box 8:, Folder 10)
    - Applications, Teaching and/or professional positions (Box 8:, Folder 11)
    - Armed Services Educational Conference (Box 8:, Folder 12)
    - Army, Department of (Box 8:, Folder 13)
    - Association of Graduate Schools - Dean Ralph Cleland (Box 8:, Folder 14)
    - Attorney General, State (Box 8:, Folder 15)
    - Auditor's reports (Box 8:, Folder 16)
    - B (Box 8:, Folder 19)
    - Bailey, Clark (Box 8:, Folder 20)
    - Belden, L. Richard (Trustee) (Box 8:, Folder 21)
    - Bequests (Box 8:, Folder 22)
    - Biographical data (Box 8:, Folder 23)
    - Bishop, Merlin (Trustee) (Box 8:, Folder 24)
    - Board material (Box 8:, Folder 25)
    - Board of Trustees - special finance committee (Box 8:, Folder 26)
    - Brammell, P. Roy - Dean, School of Education (Box 8:, Folder 27)
    - Brock, C. Raymond (Box 8:, Folder 28)
    - Budget, 1954-1955 (Box 8:, Folder 29)
    - Budget Division, State (Box 8:, Folder 30)
    - C (Box 8:, Folder 31)
    - Campus (Box 8:, Folder 32)
    - Capital outlay (Box 8:, Folder 33)
    - Carter, W. Harrison - Dean, Arts and Sciences (Box 8:, Folder 34)
    - Castleman, Francis L., Jr. (Box 8:, Folder 35)
    - Christenson, John - Commissioner of Agriculture (Box 8:, Folder 36)
    - Christian, J. O. - Director, Intercollegiate Athletics (Box 8:, Folder 37)
    - Clippings (Box 8:, Folder 38)
    - Cohen, Sumner - Men's housing (Box 8:, Folder 39)
    - Commencement - S. E. Wedberg, chairman Commencement Committee (Box 8:, Folder 40)
    - Committee letters (Box 8:, Folder 41)
    - Committee minutes (Box 8:, Folder 42)
    - Committee reports (Box 8:, Folder 43)
    - Complaints and commendations (Box 8:, Folder 44)
    - Compulsory attendance (Box 8:, Folder 45)
    - Conferences - Carlson E. Crane (Box 8:, Folder 46)
    - Congress (Box 8:, Folder 47)
    - Connecticut Citizens for the Public Schools (Box 8:, Folder 48)
    - Connecticut Public Expenditure Council (Box 8:, Folder 49)
    - Consulting work (Box 8:, Folder 50)
    - Contracts (Box 8:, Folder 51)
    - D (Box 8:, Folder 52)
    - Deans and directors (Box 8:, Folder 53)
    - Dudley, George (Trustee) (Box 8:, Folder 54)
    - E (Box 8:, Folder 55)
    - Education, School building (Box 8:, Folder 56)
    - Education, State Department (Box 8:, Folder 57)
    - En (Box 8:, Folder 58)
    - Engineering, School of - from 1955 January 1 (Box 8:, Folder 59)
    - Engleman, Finis - Commissioner of Education (trustee) (Box 8:, Folder 60)
    - Enrollment figures (Box 8:, Folder 61)
    - F (Box 8:, Folder 62)
    - Faculty appointments (Box 8:, Folder 63)
    - Finance Commissioner - James M. Loughlin (Box 8:, Folder 64)
    - Fingles, F. O. - Registrar (Box 8:, Folder 65)
    - Fontane, Patrick (Box 8:, Folder 66)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 8:, Folder 67)
    - Fraternities and sororities (Box 8:, Folder 68)
    - Fuller, Alfred C. (Trustee) (Box 8:, Folder 69)
    - Fund for the Advancement of Education - A. C. Eurich ( Ford Foundation), 1954-1955 (Box 8:, Folder 70)
    - G (Box 8:, Folder 71)
    - Gill, Joseph, N. - Commissioner of Agriculture (Box 8:, Folder 72)
    - Gleason, John H. - Director - Communications (Box 8:, Folder 73)
    - Goodchild, Franklin M. - University physician (Box 8:, Folder 74)
    - Grace-New Haven Community Hospital - Dr. Albert W. Snake,director (Box 8:, Folder 75)
    - Greetings - Welcome to students (Box 8:, Folder 76)
    - Her (Box 9:, Folder 1)
    - Hewitt, Harold G. - Dean of Pharmacy (Box 9:, Folder 2)
    - Hopkins, Bert E. - Dean, Law School (Box 9:, Folder 3)
    - I (Box 9:, Folder 4)
    - Ice hockey rink (Box 9:, Folder 5)
    - Interfraternity Council (Box 9:, Folder 6)
    - J (Box 9:, Folder 7)
    - Joint Committee on Educational Television - Ralph Steetle (Box 9:, Folder 8)
    - K (Box 9:, Folder 9)
    - Kellogg Foundation (Box 9:, Folder 10)
    - Knoblauch, A. L. (Box 9:, Folder 11)
    - L (Box 9:, Folder 12)
    - Langrock, David Theodore (Box 9:, Folder 13)
    - Legislative materials - letters (Box 9:, Folder 14)
    - Legislative material (Box 9:, Folder 15)
    - Letters of Recommendation (Box 9:, Folder 16)
    - Li (Box 9:, Folder 17)
    - Liaison Committee - State Board and Board of Trustees (Box 9:, Folder 18)
    - Lo (Box 9:, Folder 19)
    - Lodge, John - Governor of Connecticut (Box 9:, Folder 20)
    - Loughlin, Joseph M. - Director, Institute of Public Service (Box 9:, Folder 21)
    - M (Box 9:, Folder 22)
    - Mackie, Helen W. (Mrs. T. T.) (Trustee) (Box 9:, Folder 23)
    - Mahoney, Mary H. (Mrs. Robert) (Trustee) (Box 9:, Folder 24)
    - Mansfield Board of Education (Box 9:, Folder 25)
    - Map (Box 9:, Folder 26)
    - Marsh, E. Lea, Jr. (Trustee) (Box 9:, Folder 27)
    - May, Elizabeth E. - Dean, Home Economics (Box 9:, Folder 28)
    - Moyle, Wallace - Plant and maintenance (Box 9:, Folder 29)
    - McA (Box 9:, Folder 30)
    - McH (Box 9:, Folder 31)
    - McN (Box 9:, Folder 32)
    - Me (Box 9:, Folder 33)
    - Medical and dental schools (Box 9:, Folder 34)
    - Medical technicians - Dr. Kulp, Dr. Kendall (Box 9:, Folder 35)
    - Mi, 1954-1955 (Box 9:, Folder 36)
    - Military Day, 1955 May 19 (Box 9:, Folder 37)
    - Military department - Colonel Horace B. Frederick (Box 9:, Folder 38)
    - Mo (Box 9:, Folder 39)
    - N (Box 9:, Folder 40)
    - National Collegiate Athletic Association (Box 9:, Folder 41)
    - National Commission on Accrediting (Box 9:, Folder 42)